<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Super Heroes</string>

    <string name="hero1">Blaze</string>
    <string name="description1">Blaze possesses the power to manipulate fire and heat, allowing him to create and control flames at will. His fiery abilities enable him to fly by propelling himself with jets of flame. Backstory: Blaze was once an ordinary firefighter who gained his powers after a mysterious incident involving experimental chemicals. Now, he uses his abilities to fight crime and protect the city from pyromaniacs and other villains. Power Level: High Notable Fights: Defeated the arsonist villain Inferno and saved an entire city block from destruction.</string>

    <string name="hero2">Tempest</string>
    <string name="description2">Tempest can control the weather, summoning storms, lightning, and gusts of wind to aid in battle. She can also create powerful barriers of wind to protect herself and others. Backstory: Born with the ability to sense changes in the atmosphere, Tempest honed her powers through years of training in a secret monastic order. She fights to maintain balance in nature and to thwart those who would misuse its power. Power Level: Medium-High Notable Fights: Played a key role in preventing a catastrophic hurricane engineered by the villain Stormbreaker.</string>

    <string name="hero3">Aegis</string>
    <string name="description3">Aegis has the ability to generate powerful energy shields that can withstand immense force. He is also skilled in hand-to-hand combat and tactical strategy. Backstory: A former military strategist, Aegis gained his shielding abilities through a classified government experiment. He now uses his powers to protect the innocent and to safeguard national security. Power Level: Medium Notable Fights: Defended the city from an alien invasion, holding the line until reinforcements arrived.</string>

    <string name="hero4">Shadowstrike</string>
    <string name="description4">Shadowstrike can manipulate shadows and darkness, allowing him to move unseen and create constructs of solid darkness. He excels in stealth and precision strikes. Backstory: Raised in the shadows of the underworld, Shadowstrike turned away from a life of crime to become a vigilante. He uses his powers to bring justice to those who operate in the dark. Power Level: Medium Notable Fights: Infiltrated and dismantled a notorious crime syndicate, bringing its leaders to justice.</string>

    <string name="hero5">Pulse</string>
    <string name="description5">Pulse can generate and control electromagnetic waves, allowing her to disrupt electronic devices, control machinery, and create energy blasts. Backstory: Once a brilliant scientist specializing in electromagnetism, Pulse gained her powers in an accident involving a high-energy particle accelerator. Now, she fights to protect the world from technological threats. Power Level: Medium-High Notable Fights: Defeated the technopath villain Circuit, who had taken control of the city\'s power grid.</string>

    <string name="hero6">Bolt</string>
    <string name="description6">Bolt can move at lightning-fast speeds, creating bursts of electricity with his every step. He can generate electric fields and discharge bolts of lightning to stun enemies. Backstory: A former track star, Bolt gained his powers during a freak lightning storm while on a high-altitude run. He now uses his speed and electrical abilities to fight crime and keep the streets safe. Power Level: High Notable Fights: Defeated the energy-absorbing villain Dynamo in a high-speed chase across the city.</string>

    <string name="hero7">Nightstrike</string>
    <string name="description7">Nightstrike is a tech-savvy vigilante from a dystopian future,
        clad in a dark blue and silver suit powered by advanced energy conduits. His glowing armor enhances his speed,
        strength, and stealth capabilities. The light patterns across his suit adjust dynamically,
        making him nearly invisible in shadows. His mission is to protect the last free city from corrupt forces that seek to control it.
        With a billowing cape and a sharp gaze,
        Nightstrike is always ready to leap into action, relying on his wit and state-of-the-art gadgets.</string>
    <string name="hero8">Silver Specter</string>
    <string name="description8">The Silver Specter hails from a high-tech metropolis where he serves as the guardian of the skies. His suit, a combination of metallic silver and glowing neon blue, grants him superhuman agility and flight. The glowing core in his chest harnesses cosmic energy, allowing him to manipulate energy fields and deflect attacks. His strict sense of justice and formidable combat skills make him one of the most feared heroes in the city. When Silver Specter takes to the sky, enemies know there’s no escape.</string>

    <string name="hero9">Eclipse</string>
    <string name="description9">Eclipse stands tall and majestic, embodying the essence of a modern-day superhero with a twist of futuristic flair. Dressed in a high-tech armor suit, his attire is a blend of dark blues and metallic silver, with intricate patterns of glowing energy coursing through it. The suit\'s luminescent accents illuminate in sync with his movements, creating an awe-inspiring visual effect.His billowing cape, with a hint of phosphorescent shimmer, dances with the wind, adding a dramatic flair to his powerful stance. Eclipse\'s face is set with a determined expression, eyes filled with resolve and strength.The urban, dystopian cityscape surrounding him is alive with neon lights reflecting off the towering skyscrapers. The dramatic lighting from below casts a heroic aura around Eclipse, accentuating his poised readiness to leap into action. This cyberpunk environment is his battlefield, where he stands as a beacon of hope and justice amidst the chaos.</string>

    <string name="hero10">Volt Shadow</string>
    <string name="description10">Volt Shadow is a master of electromagnetic manipulation, equipped with a suit that channels lightning-like energy. His sleek, all-black armor is interwoven with electric blue lines, crackling with power. In battle, Volt Shadow uses his agility and ability to control electrical forces to overwhelm foes, leaping between skyscrapers with ease. His visor shields his identity, and his appearance strikes fear into the hearts of criminals in the neon-lit city he protects. Volt Shadow embodies the force of nature, ready to unleash his power to defend justice.</string>

    <string name="hero11">Nova</string>
    <string name="description11">Nova blazes through the dark urban skies, her suit shimmering with a cosmic blend of bright purples and deep blacks. Her armor, laced with constellations of glowing energy lines, pulses with the power of distant galaxies. A radiant energy field surrounds her, casting a halo of starlight wherever she goes.Her flowing cape, resembling the fabric of space itself, ripples with ethereal grace. Nova\'s eyes, fierce and determined, radiate confidence. The urban, neon-lit backdrop of the city mirrors the constellations on her suit, creating a harmonious blend of cosmic and cyberpunk elements. Nova is always ready to soar into action, defending the city from cosmic threats.</string>

    <string name="hero12">Titan</string>
    <string name="description12">Titan stands like a colossus amid the towering skyscrapers, his massive frame adorned with a blend of reinforced metallic armor and sleek, high-tech enhancements. The suit is predominantly dark red with accents of burnished gold, exuding strength and authority. His armor glows with crimson energy veins, pulsating with raw power.Titan\'s cape, a dark and heavy fabric, flows powerfully as he moves, symbolizing his unwavering resolve. His expression, carved in stone, reflects a sense of unyielding determination. The neon lights of the dystopian cityscape cast dramatic shadows on his imposing figure, amplifying his aura of invincibility. Titan is the stalwart guardian, a beacon of power and protection.</string>

    <string name="hero13">Spectra</string>
    <string name="description13">Spectra glides through the urban jungle with an elegant finesse, her suit a mesmerizing array of shifting colors and patterns. The sleek armor, infused with holographic technology, constantly morphs between shades of teal, magenta, and silver. Her suit is adorned with intricate circuits that pulse with prismatic light.Her cape, lightweight and semi-transparent, flows like a veil of light, adding to her ethereal presence. Spectra\'s eyes, sharp and vigilant, glow with a spectral brilliance. The neon-lit cityscape enhances the surreal quality of her appearance, blending seamlessly with the cyberpunk environment. Spectra is ever-ready to dazzle and defend, a master of light and illusion.</string>

    <string name="hero14">Vortex</string>
    <string name="description14">Vortex can create and control whirlwinds and tornadoes. He can fly using powerful updrafts and can manipulate the air to create force fields and sonic booms. Backstory: Born with the ability to sense and control air currents, Vortex honed his skills through rigorous training. He now protects the city from natural disasters and airborne threats. Power Level: Medium-High Notable Fights: Saved the city from a massive tornado generated by the rogue weather controller Tempestus.</string>

    <string name="hero15">Echo</string>
    <string name="description15">Echo has the power to manipulate sound waves. She can amplify her voice to create sonic blasts, use echolocation to navigate in darkness, and even manipulate emotions through sound. Backstory: A former musician, Echo discovered her abilities after an experimental sound wave project went awry. She now uses her sonic powers to fight crime and help those in need. Power Level: Medium Notable Fights: Neutralized the villainous hypnotist Siren by countering her mind-controlling melodies with powerful sonic waves.</string>

    <string name="hero16">Quake</string>
    <string name="description16">Quake can create and control seismic waves, causing tremors and earthquakes. He can manipulate the earth beneath him to create barriers and launch himself into the air. Backstory: After surviving a massive earthquake, Quake discovered his seismic powers and dedicated himself to protecting others from natural and man-made disasters. Power Level: High Notable Fights: Thwarted the underground terrorist group Tectonix, preventing them from triggering a catastrophic earthquake.</string>

    <string name="hero17">Aurora</string>
    <string name="description17">Aurora can manipulate light, creating dazzling illusions and blinding flashes. She can also bend light around her to become invisible and generate energy beams. Backstory: Born during a rare solar eclipse, Aurora discovered her powers at a young age. She trained in secret, honing her skills to fight evil and protect the innocent. Power Level: Medium-High Notable Fights: Defeated the light-manipulating villain Spectrum by outshining and outsmarting him in a battle of wits and illusions.</string>

    <string name="hero18">Frostbite</string>
    <string name="description18">Frostbite can generate and control ice and cold, freezing objects and creating structures of ice. He can also lower temperatures in his surroundings to immobilize foes. Backstory: Once an Arctic explorer, Frostbite gained his powers after a mystical encounter with an ancient ice deity. He uses his abilities to protect the environment and fight against ecological threats. Power Level: Medium-High Notable Fights: Stopped the villain Pyroclasm from triggering a volcanic eruption that threatened the Arctic ecosystem.</string>

    <string name="hero19">Mindwave</string>
    <string name="description19">Mindwave possesses powerful telepathic and telekinetic abilities. She can read minds, project thoughts, move objects with her mind, and create psychic shields. Backstory: A former psychologist, Mindwave developed her abilities through intense meditation and mental training. She now uses her powers to combat mental manipulation and protect against psychic threats. Power Level: High Notable Fights: Defeated the mind-controlling villain Hypnos, freeing his captives from mental enslavement.</string>

    <string name="hero20">Lumina</string>
    <string name="description20">Lumina can harness the power of the sun, creating solar blasts and beams of concentrated light. She can also fly by channeling solar energy and heal herself and others using the same energy. Backstory: Lumina\'s powers manifested during a solar eclipse, linking her abilities to the sun\'s energy. She trains rigorously to maintain control over her immense power, using it to illuminate the path of justice. Power Level: High Notable Fights: Protected the city from the shadowy villain Eclipse by outshining his darkness with her radiant solar energy.</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="hero_list">Hero List</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>

    <string name="Terms_Conditions_Title">TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">
    Welcome to [Your App Name]! By using our services, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use. Please read these terms carefully before using the application. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, please do not use our services.\n\n
    1. Acceptance of Terms\n
    By accessing and using [Your App Name], you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions, our Privacy Policy, and all applicable laws. If you do not agree, you may not use our services.\n\n
    2. Modifications to Terms\n
    We reserve the right to change these terms at any time without prior notice. You are responsible for reviewing these terms periodically to ensure your continued compliance. Your continued use of the app following any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.\n\n
    3. User Accounts\n
    a. You may need to register an account to use certain features of the app.\n
    b. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information.\n
    c. You agree to provide accurate and complete information when creating an account.\n\n
    4. Prohibited Activities\n
    a. Using the app for any unlawful purpose.\n
    b. Attempting to hack, disrupt, or compromise the security of the app.\n
    c. Engaging in fraudulent or deceptive practices.\n
    d. Distributing unauthorized advertising or spam.\n\n
    5. Intellectual Property\n
    All content available in this app, including but not limited to text, graphics, logos, and software, is the property of [Your Company Name] or its licensors and is protected by intellectual property laws. You may not reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works from the content without prior written consent.\n\n
    6. Limitation of Liability\n
    We are not responsible for any damages resulting from the use or inability to use our services. This includes but is not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages.\n\n
    7. Termination\n
    We may terminate or suspend your access to the app at our sole discretion, without notice, for any violation of these terms.\n\n
    8. Governing Law\n
    These Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of [Your Country/State]. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of [Appropriate Jurisdiction] for any disputes.\n\n
    9. Contact Information\n
    For questions about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at [support@example.com].\n\n
    By using this app, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>


</resources>